内脏出血  很久很痛
Takes a painful long time to bleed out from the gut.
克劳力  你想做什么就做什么
You can do whatever you want, Crowley.
梅塔特隆  他是个天使
Metatron -- he's an angel.
神的书记员
He's the scribe of god.
这是梅塔特隆  这是梅塔特隆
This is Metatron. This is Metatron?
我跟他们不是一类  我不是大天使
I'm not one of them. I'm not an archangel.
在上帝选我记录神之语前
I worked in the secretarial pool
我就是个小秘书
before god chose me to take down the word.
我知道了  第三项测试
I've got it. The third trial.
-是什么  -治愈一个恶魔
- What is it? - To cure a demon.
-小卡  -来帮帮忙
- Cass?! - A little help here.
阿比顿  她是个恶魔
Abbadon. She's a demon...
她是一个地狱骑士
Who, it turns out, is a knight of hell.
地狱骑士是路西法亲手挑选的
Knights of hell are hand-picked by Lucifer himself.
你脑袋里的恶魔陷阱只是为了困住你
The demon trap in your noggin is gonna keep you from smoking out.
我们要把你碎尸万段
We're gonna cut you into little steaks
然后把尸块埋入水泥
And bury each strip under cement.
如今
科罗拉多  迷失溪
真不敢相信你终于跟我来这儿了
I can't believe you finally came up here with me.
我怎么会不来呢
Why wouldn't I?
我真爱死这里了
I love this place.
我觉得终于能呼吸了
It's like...I can breathe, you know?
汤米  你没事吧
Tommy you okay?
嗯  我没事
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
什么
What?
咆哮声
The growl?
没有  可能是只熊吧
No. Maybe it's a bear.
谢丽  退后
Shelly, get back!
亲爱的  怎么了
Baby, what is wrong?
那不是熊  是个食人魔
It's not a bear. It's a wendigo.
躲进卧室里  快去
Hide in the bedroom. Right now.
躲起来  谢丽
Hide, Shelly!
汤米  我什么都没听到
Tommy, I don't hear anything.
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?
我要把他点着了
I'm gonna light his ugly ass on fire.
退后
Get back.
怎么回事
What's...h-happening?
汤米
Tommy!
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第二十二集
剪辑
-求你告诉我就这些了  -嗯
- Please tell me that's everything. - Yeah.
不  差得远呢
No, not even close.
记录者记录了
You see, the men of letters kept files
过去三百年里的每一宗恶魔附身案例
on every demonic possession for the last 300 years,
从利兹・鲍敦一直到伊卡博德・科雷恩
I mean, we've got Borden, Lizzy, all the way to Crane, Ichabod.
你感觉怎么样了
How you feeling?
说实话
Honestly, um...
我整个身体都疼
my, uh, my whole body hurts.
我觉得又恶心又饿
I feel nauseous and like I'm starving at the same time,
什么东西都一股腐肉味
and everything smells like rotting meat.
我经历过这样的宿醉
I've had that hangover.
真不好受啊
Jager, man.
也许你该休息一下  呼吸一下空气
Maybe you should, uh, take a break, get some air.
迪恩  了结这事我才会觉得好受
Dean, the only thing that's gonna make me feel better is finishing this.
好吧
All right.
我去给你弄点吃的  让你有力气
Well, I'll go get you some grub, keep your strength up.
早啊
Morning.
我喜欢这里
I like this bunker.
很整洁有序
It's orderly.
等几个月再看吧
Oh, give us a few months.
迪恩想买个乒乓球台
Dean wants to get a ping-pong table.
我听说过  那是种游戏  对吧
I've heard of that. It's a game, right?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我的伤势愈合得不够快
My wound isn't healing as quickly as I'd hoped...
但我有好转
But I am getting better.
而你却越来越糟了
And you're getting worse.
完成了两项测试  还差一项
Well, two trials down, one to go.
最后的测试  你们知道是什么了吗
And the final test, do you -- you know what it is?
我要治愈一个恶魔
I have to cure a demon.
怎么治
Of what?
我们也在查呢
That's what we're trying to figure out.
汤来了
Soup's on.
给你
There we go.
这个
I think this is, uh...
没变质
Oh, it's still good.
喝了一半的啤酒  牛肉干  三小杯花生酱
A half-drunk beer, jerky, and three peanut-butter cups?
嗯  我们补给不太够了
Yeah, we're -- we're running a little low.
我去跑一趟吧
I'll make a run.
迪恩  我可以跟你一起去
Dean, I can go with you.
迪恩
Dean.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉什么
For what?
一切
For everything.
Everything?
比如  无视我们
Like, uh... like ignoring us?
是啊
Yes.
比如带着天使石碑跑路
Or like bolting off with the angel tablet,
还给弄丢了  就因为你不信任我
then losing it 'cause you didn't trust me?
你不信任我
You didn't trust me.
-是的  -是啊
- Yes. - Yeah.
就这么说一句不行
Nah, that's not gonna cut it.
这次不行
Not this time.
所以你带着你的抱歉去死吧
So you can take your little apology and you cram it up your ass.
迪恩  我以为那么做是对的
Dean, I thought I was doing the right thing.
是啊  你总是这样
Yeah, you always do.
我们有个7B号房间吗
Hey, uh, do we have a room 7b?
哥们  别那么逼小卡
Dude, go easy on Cass, okay.
他是好人这边的
He's one of the good guys.
如果是任何别的人
Dude, if anybody else -- I mean anybody --
干那种混蛋事
pulled that kind of crap,
原则上讲  我都要捅他们脖子
I would stab them in their neck on principle.
凭什么他就能无罪豁免
Why should I give him a free pass?
因为那是小卡
Because it's Cass.
我们要找什么
What are we supposed to be looking for down here?
找跟1138号案件相关的一切
Um, anything on case 1138.
是五级地狱事件
It was a class 5 infernal event --
1957年3月8日  圣路易斯
St. Louis, March 8, 1957.
五级地狱事件
"Class 5 infernal event"?
是啊  记录者有一套评级标准
Yeah. See, the letters have this whole rating system.
《驱魔人》里面描述的也就二级
"The exorcist" would have been a class 2.
好吧  这次为什么那么特别
All right, so, what makes this puppet show so special?
很奇怪
It was weird.
怎么奇怪
Weird how?
不知道
No clue.
一卷案宗的空白处写着7B号房间
One of the files just had a note written in the margin about room 7b
和"奇怪"两个字  后面是三个惊叹号
and the word "weird" with three exclamation points.
好啊
Good times.
是啊
Yeah.
找到了
Got it.
萨姆  你来
Sammy, check this out.
那是恶魔陷阱吗
Is that a devil's trap?
占了半个房间啊
It takes up half the room.
这些锁链  上面刻着咒语
These chains -- they have spellwork etched into them.
这是个地牢啊
So we have a dungeon.
太好了
Finally.
那是什么
What do you got there?
电影之夜
Movie night?
西蒙  开始拍了
Simon, we're filming.
全世界  你们好啊
Um, hello, world.
我们要看到的这种新仪式
So this new ritual we're going to see,
新的驱魔仪式  是怎么进行的
this new type of exorcism, h-how does it work?
西蒙  过来
Simon, come.
不知道  我也是第一次
I don't know. It's my first time.
那个不是阿比顿吗
Wait, is that Abbadon?
没那么大杀气
It's not killy enough.
这肯定是被她附身的那个女孩
It's got to be the, uh, the chick she possessed.
快点  我们得开始了
Hurry. We must do it now.
死了  他们都死了
Dead! They're all dead!
你爱的每个人
Everyone you ever loved...
那些锁链跟我们地牢里的一模一样
Hey, those chains look exactly like the ones in our dungeon.
什么
In your what?
拴住的恶魔  酷啊
Demon on a leash -- cool.
[咒语]
Exorcizamus te, omnis immundus spiritus...
Hanc animam redintegra...
[咒语]
Lustra!
她死了
She's dead.
恶魔在哪
Where's the demon?
别拍了
Stop filming.
怎么回事
What happened?
你停下好吗
Will you just stop?!
的确是挺怪的
Well, that was weird...
加三个惊叹号
With three exclamation points.
那不是一般的驱魔
That wasn't a normal exorcism.
他们改了词
They changed the words.
"Lustr"应该是拉丁语中的洗刷或清洁
I believe "Lustr" is latin for wash or cleanse.
是啊  最奇怪的是他们的用词
Oh, yeah, 'cause that was the most freaky thing was the vocabulary.
那血手和胸口爆裂呢
What about the bloody high five or the chest burster?
片子上还有别的吗  比如导演评论音轨
Anything else on the film, like director's commentary,
续集呢
Sequel, maybe?
听这个
Yeah, listen to this.
年老的那个牧师  麦克斯・汤普森
The older priest, Max Thompson,
58年死了
bit the dust in '58,
但年轻的那个还活着  还住在圣路易斯
But the younger one is still alive and still lives in st. Louis.
你觉得这个怪事值得我们去一趟吗
Think this kind of weird is worth the drive?
迪恩  那些卷宗里的每一件事
Dean, everything in those folders --
附身  恶魔交易  等等一切
the possessions, the deals, all of it --
我们都见过了  但那个
we've seen that before, but that --
是全新的
That was all new.
当然值得我们去一趟了
Yeah, it's worth the drive.
好吧  我们走
All right. Let's roll.
你别去
Not you.
萨姆的伤势比我重
Sam is more damaged than I am.
是啊  可就算他受伤了  萨姆也挺过来了
Yeah, well, you know, even banged up, Sammy comes through.
-迪恩  我只想帮忙  -我们不需要
- Dean, I just want to help. - We don't need your help.
留在这儿  养好身体吧
Just stay here and -- and get better.
密苏里州  圣路易斯
汤普森神父有一些新奇的想法
Father Thompson had some unorthodox ideas,
所以记录者才会感兴趣
which is why the men of letters were interested.
怎么新奇了
Unorthodox how?
他认为恶魔可以被拯救
He believed demons could be saved.
你说"拯救"是什么意思
What exactly do you mean, "saved"?
恶魔是人的灵魂  在地狱里被扭曲玷污了
A demon is a human soul, twisted and corrupted by its time in hell.
汤普森神父认为  你可以洗净那些污秽
Father Thompson believed that you could wash that taint away
恢复他们的人性
and restore their humanity.
那么他们就继续留在他们附身的人身体里
So, what, they just stay in whatever schmuck they're possessing and -- and
然后就能升天了
get a ticket upstairs?
我也不知道啊
I wish I knew.
但这个仪式
Okay, but this -- this ritual...
能治愈恶魔
can cure a demon?
如果起效的话  或许吧
I suppose, if it worked,
但是那晚  出了很大的岔子
but that night, something went terribly wrong.
那个恶魔逃窜了出去
The demon escaped into the world,
而那个可怜的老妇人
and that poor old woman...
太可怕了
It was horrible.
我知道汤普森神父没有放弃
I know father Thompson kept trying.
还有其他附身事件  他继续了试验
There were other possessions, experiments,
但那之后我无法再那么做了
but I couldn't face that -- not again.
之后  几个月后
And then, a few months later...
他就死了
He was dead.
怎么死的
How'd that happen?
有什么把他撕裂了
Something tore him apart.
他有做
Did he keep any, uh
他做了记录或者...
did he keep records or --
你们这儿有洗手间吗
Uh do you have a-a bathroom, maybe?
谢谢
Thanks.
他没事吧
Is he all right?
不  神父
Uh, no, padre.
他跟没事差得远呢
He's...pretty damn far from all right.
我们就是为这个而来
That's why we're here.
我不明白
I don't understand.
简而言之
Well, short story is, uh,
萨姆会把撕碎你朋友的东西
Sammy there is gonna take whatever shredded your friend
和其他所有的黑眼混蛋
and every other black-eyed bitch out there,
统统了结掉
and he's gonna get rid of them for good.
他吗
He is?
他都这样了
In his condition?
神父  过去几个月
Father, over the past couple of months,
我目睹他做了很多我以为不可能的事
I've seen him do crap that I didn't even think was possible.
他的确很痛苦
I mean, sure, he's miserable and he's hurting,
但你知道吗
But you know what?
我丝毫不怀疑
There's not a doubt in my mind
他会走到终点  一点不怀疑
that he's gonna cross that finish line -- not one.
你愿意帮我们吗
So, will you help us?
我去给你拿汤普森神父的东西
I'll get father Thompson's things for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
伙计
Dude.
讲究点啊
你干什么呢
Dude!
我有钱
I -- I have money.
馅饼在哪
Where's the pie?
我们没有了
I think we're out.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我需要馅饼
I need pie.
把那个处男放下  卡西迪奥
Put the virgin down, Castiel.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
等等  你是梅塔特隆
Wait, you're Metatron.
那个大名鼎鼎的梅塔特隆吗
The Metatron?
正是
Yes.
公共场合喊我马文
In public, it's Marv.
马文
Marv.
你是卡西迪奥
And you're Castiel.
凯文・谭跟我说你的事了
Kevin Tran told me about you.
-是吗  -是啊
- He did? - Yeah.
据他说  我们有很多共同点
According to him, you and I have a lot in common.
我们都是思想自由的人
We're both free thinkers.
我们都被天堂通缉
We're both on heaven's most wanted list.
我觉得我们该联络一下感情  一起吃个饭
I thought we could socialize, maybe grab a bite.
抱歉  我们...什么
I'm sorry -- we can...what?
我一直在"休假"
Look, I've been on sabbatical.
我想了解最新的情况
I'm trying to play catch-up,
但我得找个人谈谈老家的事
but I have to talk to somebody about what's going on back home.
-老家是指天堂  -对
- And by home, you mean heaven? - Right.
我到处逛了逛
I've been looking around,
爬进了几个天使的脑子里瞧了瞧
crawling through a few divine nooks and crannies,
据我看到的情况
and from what I can see,
大天使一走  上面一团糟
without the archangels, it's a mess up there.
处于混战之中
Open warfare.
我以为  娜奥米在管理天堂
I thought Naomi was running things now.
她是这么说的吗
Is that what she told you?
娜奥米的确参与了竞争  但她不是唯一的选手
I mean, Naomi's a player -- don't get me wrong -- just one of many.
派系多不胜数
There are factions upon factions,
都在互相打斗  背叛
all fighting, betraying each other.
他们早晚会把彼此都撕烂
It's just a matter of time before they start ripping each other apart.
一切都乱套了
It's all broken.
我知道  那是我造成的
I know. I'm the one who broke it.
我曾以为我能领导我们的人
There was a time when I thought I could lead our people,
但我错了
but I was mistaken.
我造成了无数死亡
I spilled so much blood.
我试着为自己的行为赎罪  我苦修
And I've tried to atone for my sins and I did penance
为了保护我们的秘密而背叛朋友
and I betrayed my friends to protect our secrets,
但我还是失败了
but I've just failed.
现在
And now --
我明白
Look, I know.
但是现在  天使  天堂
But now the angels -- heaven --
需要有人去帮忙
need someone to come to the rescue.
他们需要我们
They need us.
-我们  -对  想象一下
- Us? - Yeah. Just -- just picture it.
我们去拯救他们  挽救大局
We ride to the rescue, save the day --
那说起来多好听啊
Make a great story.
天使就像一个庞大的有问题的家庭
Look, the angels are like a big, dysfunctional family.
我们得把他们都锁在一个屋里
We need to lock them all in a room
直到把这些问题都解决了
until we work these problems out --
所有的派系  你和我
All the factions, you, me --
像一场巨大的家庭集会吗
What, like a big family meeting?
没错
Exactly.
所以我们得关闭天堂
Which is why we have to shut down heaven.
什么
What?
你喜欢可丽饼吗
Do you like crepes?
等等
Wait -
奥海的尤金妮做的苹果可丽饼最好吃了
Eugenie's in Ojai makes the greatest caramel apple crepes.
梅塔特隆  马文
Metatron -- Marv.
我找不到小卡
I can't find Cass.
你觉得他走了吗
You think he blew town?
像他的风格
Sounds like him.
看来
So it turns out that, uh,
汤普森神父把恶魔治愈的测试都做了记录
father Thompson recorded all of his demon-cure tests.
这个是最后一个
This one here, this was the last one --
两天后他就死了
Two days before he died.
现在是1958年8月3日
The date is August 3, 1958.
这是第19次试验  第一小时
This is trial 19, hour 1.
实验对象  彼得・肯特
My subject is Peter Kent.
肯特先生是两个幼子的父亲
Mr. Kent is the father of two young sons,
三周之前  他被一个恶魔附身了
and three weeks ago, he was possessed by a demon.
我现在要问你一个问题
I'm going to ask you a question now.
你钻进肯特先生的身体  吃掉他的孩子
When you crawled into Mr. Kent and ate his children,
是什么感受
how did it feel?
很兴奋
Orgasmic.
已经注入第一剂
The first dose has been administered.
知道牧师给头号爸爸注射的是什么吗
Do we know what padre was dosing number-one dad up with?
他自己净化的血液
Uh, yeah, his own purified blood.
怎么净化的
Purified how?
他开始之前
Before he started,
汤普森神父去忏悔了
Father Thompson went to confession.
这是19号审判  第二小时
This is trial 19, hour 2.
你吃他的孩子时  是什么感觉
When you ate his children, how did it feel?
很有嚼头
Stringy!
已经注入第二剂
The second dose has been administered.
第四小时
Hour 4.
你吃他的孩子时
When you ate his children --
吃屎吧
Kiss my ass!
-是什么感觉  -软软的
- How did it feel? - Soft.
已经注入第六剂
The sixth dose has been administered.
停下
Stop.
-是...  -求你了
- How... - Please.
什么...
...did it...
感觉
...feel?
住手
Stop!!
第八小时  实验对象已经准备好了
Hour 8, the subject is prepped.
[咒语]
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus.
[咒语]
Hanc animam redintegra, lustra!
Lustra!
你吃他的孩子时  是什么感觉
When you ate his children, how did it feel?
他们在尖叫
They were screaming...
我却在笑
and I laughed.
我为什么会笑
Why did I laugh?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
上帝啊  我是个恶魔
God, I was a monster.
但你现在又变回了人
But now you are a man again.
你被拯救了
And you have been saved.
他刚刚...治愈了一个恶魔吗
Did he just... cure a demon?
或许吧
Maybe.
咱们能测试一下这个方法吗
Could we take this hoodoo on a test drive?
驱魔法就在这里
Um, I mean, I have the exorcism right here.
我们只需要血液  圣地  和一个恶魔
All we need is the blood, consecrated ground, and a demon.
怎么做  召唤一个恶魔  然后困住它
So, what? We summon a demon, trap it --
或者我们用我们已经抓到的一个
Or -- or we use one that we've already tagged.
爸爸的战地外科医生手术包还在吗
Do we still have dad's old army field surgeon's kit?
在行李箱里  怎么了
It's in the trunk. Why?
我们该把那个讨厌鬼拼起来了
Yeah, I think it's time we put Humpty Dumpty back together again.
你为什么走了
Why did you leave?
饿着肚子可不能谈这事
I can't have this conversation on an empty stomach.
您的菜
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
您要点什么吗
Can I get you anything?
咖啡  谢谢
Coffee, please.
好的  外套很酷[凉]啊
Sure. Cool coat.
没有  其实很保暖
No, it's actually quite warm.
可爱又幽默  好吧
Cute and funny -- okay.
早知道我就选个帅点的皮囊了
I should have picked a better-looking vessel.
你说关闭天堂是什么意思
What did you mean, we can shut down heaven?
你知道的  那些测试
Oh, you know, the trials --
上帝设下的紧急情况按钮
God's little "Pull in case of emergency",
如果利维坦逃了出来
the Leviathans get out of control,
就把它们扔回炼狱
you put them in purgatory.
如果恶魔们玩得太过火了  扔回地狱
Demons get a little too demonic, toss 'em into hell.
天使们过于膨胀了  关上天国之门
Angels get uppity, slam the pearly gates.
你是说你知道关闭天堂的测试
Are you saying you know the trials to close heaven?
是我记下来的
I wrote 'em down.
这种事情你可忘不了
It's not something you forget.
我觉得  单独待会儿对天使来说不是坏事
Look, I think a little alone time would be good for the angels.
至少能够...
At the very least, it would s--
能够避免让上面的争斗祸及下面
It would stop the fighting up there from spilling out down here,
因为那是必然结果  一向如此
which will happen. It always does.
你要完成这些测试吗
You're gonna complete these tests?
不
No.
我干不了
I can't.
我只是个秘书  仅此而已
I am a pencil pusher, always have been.
我不够强壮
I'm not strong enough.
而你呢  你是个斗士
But you -- you are a warrior.
我有办法
I've got the plan.
你来付诸实践
You've got the muscle.
我们合力  必能成功
We can do this.
天堂需要你的帮助  卡西迪奥
Heaven needs your help, Castiel.
我是罪魁祸首
I am the one that caused these problems.
确实该我来收拾这个烂摊子
I should be the one to fix them.
但你必须知道  这事可不容易
But you understand this is, um, not going to be easy.
我懂
I understand.
不  你不懂
No, you don't.
看见那个女招待了吗
See our waitress?
她就是第一道测试  把她的心挖出来
She's the first trial -- got to cut her heart out.
什么
What?
不  她只是...
No, she's...
她只是个女孩
She's just a girl.
不  她不是
No, she isn't.
她是个拿非利人  禁忌之人
She's a Nephilim, an abomination.
她是天使和凡人的后代
She's the offspring of an angel and a human?
-那不是禁止的吗  -是禁止的
- I thought that wasn't allowed. -It's not.
世界上仅此一个  就是她了
There's only one on earth, and you are looking at it.
但她并没选择做一个拿非利人  她是无辜的
But she didn't choose to be a nephilim, so she's innocent.
她是无辜的
Yes, she is.
我告诉你了  这事不容易
I told you it wasn't gonna be easy.
如果你想完成这个  卡西迪奥
But if you want to do this, Castiel,
如果你真心想这么做
if you really want to do this,
你得问问自己什么才是最重要的
you got to ask yourself what's more important --
是她的生命还是你的家族
Her life or your family?
你觉得这样能行
So you really think this will work?
老弟  我们有了针线
Dude, we got needles. We got thread.
《年轻的科学怪人》我们都看过几千次了
We've seen "Young Frankenstein" about a thousand times.
我们没问题的
Yeah, we're golden.
这会很恶心的
This is gonna be disgusting.
早啊  帅哥们
Morning, sunshines.
起效了
It worked.
你欠我一瓶啤酒
You owe me a beer.
我欠你们二位好多啊
And I owe you both so, so much.
我真等不及要扯下你们漂亮的绿眼睛了
I can't wait to tear out those pretty green eyes.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
我们觉得你用不上爪子了
We figured kitty didn't need her claws.
那我就把你们踩死  那也不错
Then I'll stump you to death. It'll be swell.
这你也别想了
Yeah, that's not gonna happen, either.
记得那颗子弹吗
The bullet -- remember?
你像个小贱人那样坐好
So you sit there like a good little bitch.
我们要把这块地圣化
We're gonna consecrate the ground,
你要老实坦白
and you're gonna get to fessing up.
-这话耳熟啊  -我看未必
- Oh, I know this tune. - I doubt that.
麦克斯・汤普森神父
Father Max Thompson,
1910年10月12日生
born October 12, 1910.
死于1958年8月5日
Died August 5, 1958.
你以为是谁把他撕碎了
Who do you think ripped him apart?
大本营那里听说了麦克斯干的捣乱事
Word got back to home office that Maxie was messing with things,
于是我们杀一儆百
so we made an example.
虽然不是我最有美感的一次杀戮  但很有效
It wasn't my most artful kill, but it was effective.
意外惊喜是
And bonus --
他死前跟我说了乔茜・桑兹的事
Before he died, he told me all about Josie Sands.
我找到了她  借她的身体找到了记录者
I found her, and I rode her into the men of letters.
我对他们做的事  那才叫艺术
And what I did to them, that was art.
那么你知道麦克斯在做什么了
So you know what Max was doing?
他说了个大致
Fella screamed the basics...
但那不会成功的
But it'll never work.
你就那么安慰自己吧
You keep telling yourself that.
666来电[666指魔鬼]
好啊  孩儿们
Hello, boy.
克劳力
Crowley.
Crowley?
那个推销员
The salesman?
他是地狱之王
Try the king of hell.
你开我心吧
This is a joke, right?
留在这儿
Stay.
等等
Hold on.
你怎么拿到这个号码的
How'd you get this number?
要紧事先说
Ah, first things first --
你穿着什么呢
What are you wearing?
行了  给我挂了  马上挂掉
Oh, okay, hanging up now. Hang up.
好吧  我不是打来闲聊的
Fine. This isn't a social call.
我在想
I was wondering.
你们最近读报纸了吗
You lads been reading the papers,
比如昨天的《丹佛时报》
say, Denver Times from yesterday?
没有吗
No?
你们该看看  令人震惊
Well, you should. It's side-splitting.
不管了  我把地址发给你
What the hell -- I'm sexting you an address.
去看看吧
Check it out.
回头再聊  拜拜了
Then we'll talk. Cheerio.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
克劳力
Crowley?
迷失溪发生诡异死亡事件
在这儿呢  死者名叫汤米・科林斯
Here it is. Vic's name is Tommy Collins.
汤米  怎么这么耳熟
Tommy. Why do I know that name?
汤米・科林斯
Well, Tommy Collins,
我们好久以前从食人魔手里把他救了下来
we saved him from a wendigo like forever ago.
怎么  克劳力把他的头炸下来了吗
Okay, and, what, you think that Crowley blew his head off?
这是什么情况
Well, what are we dealing with here?
恶魔和食人魔联手了吗
Some sort of demon-wendigo team-up?
不知道
Uh, no clue.
我们回头再纪念汤米吧
All right, well, we'll pour one out for Tommy later.
至于克劳力  去他的
As far as Crowley goes, screw him.
我们具备了一切让他永远休息的条件了
We got everything we need to put him in a permanent time-out.
不不不
No. No! No! No! No!
她跑了
She's gone.
她  该死的
She's -- son of a bitch!
迪恩
Dean!
Dean.
是克劳力来的短信
It's a text message from Crowley --
印第安纳州  兴隆市  绿叶街545号  306室
是印第安纳州  兴隆市的一个地址
An address in Prosperity, Indiana.
兴隆市
Prosperity?
我们在那儿接过一桩案子吧
Didn't we work a case there?
就是女巫和烘培食品那桩
Yeah, yeah, the one with the witches and the baked goods.
怎么  他又去找那里什么人的麻烦了吗
So what? He's going after somebody there now?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们得去看看
We got to check it out.
-你知道是陷阱  -当然是陷阱
- Well, you know it's a trap. - Of course it's a trap.
但是陷阱意味着有恶魔  我们现在需要一个
But a trap means demons, and we could use one right now.
印第安纳州  兴隆市
萨姆
Sam.
那是詹妮吗
Is that...Jenny?
你是个好女孩  詹妮・克莱恩
You were a great gal, Jenny Klein.
魔鬼来电
克劳力  你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing, Crowley?
小鹿  这还不明显吗
Oh, moosie, isn't it obvious?
我在杀你们救过的每一个人
I'm killing everyone you've ever saved --
困境中的少女  无辜的傲慢者
The damsels in distress, the innocent whippersnappers,
险些被吸血鬼吃掉的人  他们所有人
The would-be vampire chow -- all of them.
你怎么知道
How do you even know --
我有线人和强大的研究小组
I have my sources and a cracking research team.
《凶鬼恶灵》
你们俩到一个地方
When you boys hit a town,
通常会搞得人仰马翻
you tend to leave a mess.
你们大概在想
Now, you're probably wondering
我的手下怎么没有留在那里赶你们走
why my droogs aren't in there giving you the bum's rush,
我们就开门见山地说吧  好吗
so let's brass these tacks, shall we?
每12小时  我就要把一个人开肠破肚
I'm gonna gut one person every 12 hours
直到你们俩把恶魔石碑给我送来
until you bring me the demon tablet
并且终止这个荒谬的测试
and stop this whole trials nonsense.
我们没有石碑  凯文拿走了
We don't have the tablet. Kevin took it and --
我抓住了凯文
I took Kevin.
然后有人又救走了他
Then someone took him back.
云端传话下来  说不是天堂
Word from the cloud is that it wasn't heaven.
所以世界上最聪明伶俐的小先知
So either the cutest little prophet in the world
要么和你们俩在一起
is with you two lads,
要么你们最好赶紧找到他
or you better find him tout-bloody-suite
因为时间在飞逝
because time, she is a-wasting.
现在你们在想办法阻止我
About now, you're thinking of ways to stop me.
你们做不到的
You won't be able to,
但是你们还是会尝试  因为你们就这样
but you'll try because that's what you do.
你们尽力而为
You -- you try.
该进行实例教学了
So, time for an object lesson.
印第安纳波利斯
Indianapolis,
艾薇旅馆  116房
the Ivy motel, room 116.
你们还有57分钟
You have 57 minutes.
你打算怎么办  卡西迪奥
What's it gonna be, Castiel?
莎拉
Sarah.
萨姆
Sam?
我是莎拉・布莱克
I'm Sarah Blake.
我是萨姆
I'm Sam.
怎么了
What's going on?
我知道你们是什么
I know what you are.
我能看到你们的光环
I could see your halos.
我们知道你是什么  禁忌
And we know what you are, abomination.
拜托  我不是
Please, I'm not.
我尽量友善待人
I try to be nice.
我只想过自己的生活
I just want to live my life.
我们知道
We know.
我很遗憾
I am sorry.
你会的
You will be.
玩得开心吗
Having fun?
你想要禁忌
You want an abomination?
我让你见识一下禁忌的厉害
I'll show you an abomination.
一个名叫克劳力的恶魔
So a demon named Crowley
要在16分钟后杀死我
is gonna kill me in...16 minutes.
不
No.
他不会得逞的
No, he's not.
莎拉  好久不见
Sarah, long time.
你在印第安纳波利斯干什么
What you doing in Indy?
我在帮我爸爸物色房产买卖
I...was scouting an estate sale for my dad.
我们要在这里布满恶魔陷阱
Look, we're gonna put devil's traps everywhere --
窗户  门
The windows, the door.
我们有圣水
We've got holy water,
循环播放的驱魔咒
an exorcism ready to play on a loop,
通过那扇门的
and anything that comes through that door --
都会变成肉泥
It's meat.
我知道这很疯狂
Look, I know this is insane,
但是我们常常这样
but insane is kind of what we do.
我们会保护你
We'll keep you safe.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  就这样吗
Okay? That's it?
你以前也这么做过
You've done it before.
这个以前没有
That's new.
是啊  我
Yeah, I...
他叫伊恩
His name is Ian.
他是搜索与营救队的
He works search and rescue.
看来我喜欢这个类型的
Guess I have a type.
我们的女儿  贝丝  再有一个月就满周岁了
Our daughter, Bess -- she'll be one in a month.
那...很好
That's, uh, great.
真心的
I mean it.
我真的
I'm really, uh...
我真为你高兴
I'm really happy for you.
谢谢  萨姆
Thanks, Sam.
你呢
And what about you?
我
Me?
几乎没什么变化吧
Pretty much the same, I guess.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
你不一样了
You're not the same.
已经好几年了
Look, it's been years,
我都无法想象你都经历了什么
and I can't even imagine the things you've been through.
但是  说不清
But I don't know.
你看起来
You just seem
更专注  更自信  好像
..more focused, confident, like...
好像知道自己想要什么
...like you know what you want.
你成熟了  萨姆
You grew up, Sam.
但我还是喜欢你以前的发型
I do miss the old haircut, though.
克劳力
Crowley.
五
Five...
四
Four...
三
Trios...
二
Zwei...
一
...uno.
莎拉
Sarah! Hey!
听我说  你能听见我说话吗
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Can you hear me?
莎拉
Sarah!
她要死了  你们什么也做不了
She's dying, and there's nothing you can do about it.
你个婊子养的
You son of a bitch!
其实是女巫养的
Son of a witch, actually.
我妈咪教会了我一些招数
My mommy taught me a few tricks.
是咒语  快找魔法袋
It's a spell. Find the hex bag.
我考虑过派几个大块头去
I thought of sending in a few of my bruisers,
让他们好好玩玩
really letting them go to town.
但是呢  测试一杀死了一只地狱之犬
But then, well, trial one was kill a hellhound.
测试二是从地狱拯救一个灵魂
Trial two was rescue a soul from the pit.
从此往后
So, from here on,
我要让一切和地狱有关的东西
I'm gonna keep everything hell-related --
恶魔等等的  离你们远点
Demons, et cetera -- away from you.
完全是出于安全考虑
Safe side and all that --
再说了  我觉得这样很合适
Plus, I just thought it seemed fitting.
据我了解  小萨姆让那小妞无法呼吸
From what I understand, Sammy took that bird's breath away.
怎么说的来着
What's the line?
拯救他人  猎杀凶鬼恶灵  家族事业
Saving people, hunting things -- the family business.
我觉得你们救下的人
Well, I think the people you save,
你们用他们来证明你们可悲的人生有些用处
they're how you justify your pathetic little lives.
酗酒  附带伤害
The alcoholism, the collateral damage,
你们所造成的一切痛苦
the pain you've caused --
唯一一件能让你们每夜安睡的事情
The one thing that allows you to sleep at night,
唯一一件就是知道这些人们还活着
the one thing is knowing that these folks are out there,
因为你们  他们还快乐健康地活着
still out there happy and healthy because of you,
你们这两个伟大的该死的英雄
you great, big, bloody heroes.
你会没事的
Hey! Hey! Hey! You're gonna be okay.
-莎拉  -他们是你们毕生的杰作
- Sarah? - They're your life's work,
我要把这一切一点一点撕碎
and I'm going to rip it apart piece by piece
因为我能做到
because I can,
因为你们无法阻止我
because you can't stop me,
还因为  当他们都死去
and because when they're all gone,
你们还剩下什么呢
what will you have left?
不  不不
No. No, no, no.
不
No.
不  求你了  不要
No, please, no.
你们想让那些人继续活着
You want to keep those people alive.
我想要完全彻底的投降
I want complete and utter surrender.
石碑  测试  全部都放弃
The Tablet, the Trials -- you'll give them up,
否则我们就继续这么玩吧
or we'll keep doing this dance.
你们选择吧  亲爱的
Your choice, my darlings.
你还好吗
You okay?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我知道现在情况很糟
Look, I know it's bad right now, okay,
但是我们还是得按计划
but we stick to the plan.
关上地狱之门
We shut down hell.
到底怎么做
How, exactly?
我们找到一个恶魔
We get a demon --
你听到克劳力的话了
You heard Crowley.
他不会让任何恶魔接近我们
He's not gonna let one near us,
没有恶魔  我们只能傻坐着
and without a demon, all we can do is sit back
看着所有我们认识的人  我们救下的人
and watch people we know, people we saved,
像莎拉一样死去
die like Sarah.
那你是什么意思
So what are you saying?
我是说
I'm saying...
也许这场争斗我们赢不了
Maybe this isn't one we can win.
也许我们就该接受条件
Maybe we should just take the deal.
我们会有办法的
We'll figure this out.
我们可以
We will.
我们会做到的
Man, we'll get it done.
我们会像以往一样打个漂亮仗
We'll kick it in the ass like we always do.
你要和我一起吗
Are you with me?